(This story is entirely fictional)
Here?
(Yes.)
(Based on novel Doctor Qin: Executer)
(This is the deposit.)
(Ten times more after it's done.)
(The blueprint is under the workbench.)
(Design blueprint)
Will this thing work?
(Prepare materials
according to the blueprint.)
(It's very safe.)
(Just don't do anything unnecessary.)
(I'll guide you to the first treasure.)
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
♪Shadows roll over the girl's wall♪
♪The sunset is nailed to the tombstone♪
♪They say a cat has nine lives♪
♪Guess how many lives
I've lived through♪
♪The fluorescent powder
tears the scars open♪
♪Fresh blood feeds the crocodiles♪
♪They stroll down the hallway
with smirks♪
♪When the prey breaks free♪
♪The hunter masks up and runs♪
♪Don't ask how I'll close the net♪
♪Fire burns their footprints
into one blaze♪
♪This world often can't digest♪
♪The sins it swallows,
dawn spits on the shore♪
♪Crocodile hits bottom♪
♪The water lies still♪
♪A cat has nine lives,
and keeps a tab on every single one♪
Miss,
you're amazing.
It came out just like your blueprint.
(To kill someone,)
(you have to learn some skills.)
♪A cat has nine lives,
and keeps a tab on every single one♪
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 17=
In position.
It has strong recoil.
First time using it, don't rush.
Press and hold the preheat button.
Wait for the indicator light
before firing.
It'll be more stable that way.
Okay.
Armored cash truck.
My whole future depends on this.
Let's get rich...
Twenty-nine.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-seven.
♪I wish I could become...♪
No obvious damage
to the subcutaneous tissue of the neck.
(Forensic DNA Area)
The major blood vessels are intact.
This matches our initial assessment
from the scene.
Dr. Qin,
don't you think
his injuries are too concentrated?
Look here.
A normal fire would cause
relatively even burning
on the body surface.
But this area of his
shows penetrating damage
to the chest and surrounding tissue.
Torn edges, missing tissue.
That'd take a massive burst
of high energy.
Even more unusual
is around the occipital bone.
A complete fracture
around the foramen magnum
is very clear.
The foramen magnum's separated
from the skull.
But the ring of skull around it
is still connected to the spine.
This simply cannot be caused
by human force.
The victim's head extends left,
and the fracture line widens.
This means the force comes
from lower right or upper left.
But his right shoulder joint
is dislocated downward.
What kind of impact can
simultaneously produce
two forces in opposite directions?
An explosion.
An explosion?
Here.
The DNA results are out.
It's Qiao Shengchan!
Shiyu, go on.
The blast point
was above the right shoulder.
It exploded in midair.
So there's no crater on the ground.
The shockwave pushed the skull upward
and the shoulder downward.
The right ear was closest
to the blast source,
causing bilateral eardrum perforation
and a ring fracture at the skull base.
Oh my God, what is this?
Use your imagination.
This is...
a homemade rocket launcher?
Considering all the injury patterns
and the position of the device,
if the victim operated it
on his own shoulder,
then it can be classified
as an accident.
An accident?
You call this an accident?
Qiao's an illiterate thug
just out of prison.
Never mind whether he could do it.
Just talk about why.
Why would he go through all that trouble
to make such a big thing?
And why choose the side of a highway
to blow himself up?
Qiao Shengchan has
an elementary school education.
No military background,
and no mechanical knowledge.
(Longfan Police)
For him to build a weapon on his own
is absolutely impossible.
Unless
someone is directing him
or providing the blueprint.
Even if the blueprint was given
by someone else,
what about the motive?
What was his motive?
Building such a crude
but highly lethal device,
there must be some purpose.
This kind of homemade launcher
among civilians
is mainly used for illegal hunting.
Hunting?
Haha.
He's going to hunt rabbits
with this thing?
Is rabbit meat expensive enough
or does he want to add himself
to the dish?
No.
Look at its size and structure.
The charge it can carry
far exceeds
the power needed
to hunt any land animal.
In the fuse residue,
we detected an extremely unstable,
specially catalyzed explosive compound.
This compound
has controllable stability
under normal firing conditions.
But once the preheat time
exceeds thirty seconds,
its stability drops exponentially,
eventually causing a chamber explosion
instead of firing.
A time bomb?
This is a psychological trap.
The killer knew
someone like Qiao
would get nervous and hesitate
operating this weapon
for the first time.
And the longer he waits and prepares,
the closer he gets to death.
This is a bizarre suicide?
This isn't a preheat button.
It's a chemical timer.
What do you mean?
It's pretty hot.
(Stopwatch countdown)
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Why is it so hot?
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
(Stopwatch countdown)
The killer knew
an amateur like Qiao
would wait and hesitate.
Yet the longer he waits,
the closer he gets to death.
(Die!)
Qiao directly caused
Su Qingchen's disability.
But he's also
a disposable pawn.
He didn't even know why he died.
(Rated capacity: 6 passengers)
Are you sympathizing with him?
It's not sympathy.
Those consumed
by anger and hatred
eventually all become tools.
We need to find the person behind it.
Find her,
so we can make her stop.
(Qin Ming,)
(we must get into the same university.)
(Then things will get better for us.)
(Maybe we'll share the same future.)
Hello, police?
Murder!
Longfan Park.
A woman's body.
It's a woman's body.
She's alive!
A living woman!
Transferred from the local police.
Her name is Zhang Lanfen.
She's in a coma.
Her family had reported her missing
a while back.
But no link to our cases
was ever found.
It's not that simple.
Let's look for more clues.
Okay.
Let's go.
Where to?
Her home.
Ziyan, what's the situation?
From the initial look,
no signs of a struggle at the scene.
But something feels off.
There are drag marks.
(Sketch book)
This isn't creation.
This is clearly peeping.
So perverted.
She really wasn't creating art.
She was reproducing everything
she saw about Jin Keke.
Before she disappeared,
she monitored Jin Keke
in an almost obsessive way.
Mr. Han,
there's another one here.
Who's this?
Qiao Shengchan?
Doesn't look like him.
Jin Keke has an accomplice?
(Cases Linked to Jin Keke)
Zhang Lanfen, 29 years old.
(Serve the People with Dedication)
Freelance painter.
Moved in half a year ago.
According to system data,
and the last time the landlord saw her,
she's been missing for at least a week.
Coincidentally,
Song Yalan lives across from her.
They could see each other at home.
Ziyan,
your notes are like encrypted text.
I can't understand them.
You'd better explain the details.
This case is not easy to investigate.
This place is a maze.
It's an old area poorly managed.
No registration, fake IDs,
and short-term stays are common.
Basically, people don't interact.
Let alone any witnesses.
But there must be some social life.
Even if no WeChat or Weibo updates,
won't her parents or friends
notice her missing?
Young people these days
are always on their phones, right?
But I do go several weeks
without messaging my parents.
That's the key point.
Zhang Lanfen has almost no social ties.
She lives in seclusion.
No fixed work circle.
We checked
all her social media accounts.
Almost zero updates in three years.
The last phone record
was a call to a delivery station
a month ago.
That's a common social phenomenon now.
Now even if someone disappears,
it might not be noticed for a long time.
Considering all these coincidences,
her disappearance might be related
to Jin Keke.
But Zhang Lanfen
doesn't fit Jin's revenge logic at all.
Maybe Jin discovered
Zhang Lanfen was watching her,
so she kidnapped her.
Who's the man in this painting?
It's me.
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪